Don!
There are always two truths!
Detective Juriaki!
I'm going to tell you the truth.
Let's go.
I'm really happy to have met everyone.
This program is a program where 6
people who are active to promote
something exciting
to the world by challenging various
things.
The world is a big place.
We challenge everything we want to do.
We will prove the exciting future.
Happy New Day
The truth is always two.
I'm a famous detective, Juriaki.
New episode updated every Wed. 1700 JST
We settled the guest house at Smancon.
Well, what are we doing today?
The manager seems to be there, so we
want to do a peek.
Fans!
Let's go!
Here she is.
Thank you for watching!
What were you doing?
Are you drinking honey?
I'm going to drink honey to get my
throat in shape.
Our manager, Tsujino-san, is drinking
honey and coffee.
You're an adult.
I'm 21 years old.
She's a beautiful woman.
I can't drink it, though.
You're a beautiful woman.
I'm a man.
I'll give you honey later.
Thank you.
I drank it.
Coffee?
I drank coffee.
What's wrong with you today?
I'm going to tell you the secret of
Tsujino-san.
I met a fan the other day.
Thank you.
Thank you for celebrating with
everyone.
How was the cake?
It was delicious.
The strawberry was juicy and delicious.
What was the most fun thing at the
birthday party?
Was it the balloon?
Two balloons.
Did you want to go inside?
I've been inside.
That's great.
It was an old birthday party.
Did you break it?
I went inside and broke the balloon.
Doesn't it stick?
It's like a balloon that can be put in.
Please try it again next time.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you.
Are you ready?
It's time.
I asked Tsujino-san to say something.
The truth is...
Tsujino-san can't drink coffee.
Yes.
Yes, that's it.
Thank you very much.
Well, Tsujino-san, please eat this
later.
Thank you very much.
I got a Chiroro chocolate.
I'm glad you got coffee.
Thank you very much.
If I have this, I might be able to
drink coffee.
Really?
Please drink coffee.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
Please do your best.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
I'm sorry.
We are in the middle of Tokibana, but
here is a breaking news.
Hello everyone.
I'm Kanami, a member of the group,
Super Tokimeki Blue.
Thank you for waiting.
This week, I, Uchiho, brought you the
Tokimeki Breaking News as soon as
possible.
I think you'll be happy with this
week's Tokimeki Breaking News.
I can't wait to announce it.
Speaking of which, the 2Days Arena
performance will be held in August.
I'm sure you're all looking forward to
it.
The last Z-Haneda live was also great.
It's been a while since I've seen you
all.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I hope it can be held.
Speaking of which, the Hiori Birthday
Party will be held on August 8th.
I'll be 19 years old. Congratulations!
Hiyorin, who is always said to be like
a baby, is already 19 years old.
It's hard to believe.
Let's get married together!
Speaking of waiting, I'm going to be a
YouTuber.
I'll do my best to upload videos again.
Please wait for me.
It's about time.
I'll show you something on theously
right now.
Don't forget the headline with mentions
due in your mind.
On August 26th, I will release the new
single, Tomorrow's Strongest Theory, a
super-exciting promotional song.
It's a coupling song.
It's the new song that I performed for
the first time at the ZEPP HANEDA.
It's the new song, Koi no Jackal!
Koi no Jackal will be broadcasted on
the music streaming sites from tonight
at 24 o'clock, which is the same as the
26th release date!
I'm looking forward to it!
I performed this song for the first
time at that time.
How did you feel when you first heard
this song?
I thought it was a very fresh song.
I don't think there are many songs that
I can sing with love like this.
This song is a bit novel.
It's a song that you can really get
excited about.
The choreography is also a bit like
rugby.
It's a really interesting song.
It's a song that you can dance and get
excited with everyone.
I hope you all remember this dance.
I hope we can dance together at the
Arena Park on the 22nd and 23rd.
It's not decided yet, but please look
forward to it.
Is that okay?
I'm sleepy.
That's all for today's Toki Baro.
Thank you for watching Toki Baro.
It will be broadcasted from 24 o'clock,
so please check it out.
Please enjoy Toki Baro after this.
That's all for today.
See you.
Please subscribe to our channel!
Please subscribe to my channel!
I'm 21 years old.
Today is the birthday party of Kanamin.
Congratulations!
I have one month left.
Thank you.
We are looking forward to your support.
Kanami, Julia, Toko, Haruka, Aki,
Hiyori.
Super-exciting Anniversary.
Rock'n'Roll!
Good luck!
Thank you for your viewing.
Our birthday party has started!
Thank you so much!
This birthday party will be broadcast
live.
It will be on the screen.
Let's get excited together!
Everyone, I turned 21 on June 2nd!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
It's been a month since I turned 21.
I'm so happy to have a birthday party
like this!
Let's enjoy together!
Kanami! Happy birthday!
I'm a big fan of Kanamin, but I only
have Julia as my FC.
I'm looking forward to working with
you!
Let's shake hands!
Air hug!
Cute!
That's nice!
I'm looking forward to working with
you!
I'm Suda Aki, also known as Aki-chan!
Kanamin!
I always call myself Kanami-chan, but
I'm going to call myself Kanamin!
I'm Kanamin!
Cute!
Kanamin-chan!
I'm Kanamin-chan!
I'm not really around, so I'm not that
new.
But please call me Kanamin!
Kanamin!
I'm calling you!
I haven't called anyone yet!
Then, we're going to call you Kanamin-
chan from now on!
Kanamin-chan!
This is awkward!
I thought I was going to cry!
I was talking about this after the
rehearsal, but Kanamin is crying a lot.
I don't know what's going on, but I'm
crying.
Don't cry!
Kanamin!
Happy birthday!
Don't cry!
What's this?
This is a balloon.
There's a cake on top of it.
There's a cake, right?
Thank you!
It's okay. There's a real cake in the
dressing room.
Let's eat it!
Thank you!
Kanamin, hold this.
It's so cute!
Happy birthday to you! Happy birthday,
dear Kanamin!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday!
Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you so much!
I could hear your voices!
Thank you so much!
I'm so happy to have this birthday
party every year.
I remember the old days.
I think it's a miracle that I can be
here.
I used to be worried about many things.
I used to think that I was not good
enough to be in this group.
But now I'm happy that I can continue
this activity.
I'm so happy that I can do this because
of your support.
You always give me a lot of warm words.
I'm so happy that I can meet you.
I wouldn't be here if it wasn't for
you.
I'm so happy that I can meet you.
I'm so happy that I can meet you and
stay here.
My personal goal is to be able to sing
and perform well enough to surprise you.
I'm so happy if you support me.
My dream is to be the best me.
I have a dream of Budokan since long
time ago.
If I believe in my dream, I think I can
make it come true.
I think I can make it come true with my
members, everyone who always supports
me, and my staff.
I will do my best to be a group that
continues to grow and love many people.
I will do my best as a member of the
Super Tokimeki Advertisement and as a
member of the Juju Kaname.
Please continue to support me.
I want to be myself that can disappear
a little
My true love is so exciting that I
can't stop
On the way home, we become a little
weird
Thank you!
I was nervous
Thank you very much
What is it?
It's a can of canapes!
Canapes!
Wow!
It says canapes!
I'm so happy!
Yay!
Thank you!
The strawberry is delicious!
It looks delicious!
Thank you!
I want to be a princess.
Oh, that's right.
Thank you so much for celebrating
today.
I think it's a birthday party full of
my personality.
I hope you enjoy it.
I'll do my best, so please support me.
Thank you so much.
It's hard.
Happy birthday!
Thank you!
The rainbow-colored bench is still
waiting
The bench is getting whiter
Go! Go! Tomorrow!
The best!
Please subscribe to my channel!
Stretch out your hands
I can't take it anymore
I'll meet you with a kiss
Swimming, swimming
Stretch out your hands
I can't take it anymore
I'll meet you with a kiss
I'm happy just to be like this
I'm happy at this time
The color of the kiss is sexy
It never changes
The first day of the concert
I love you, I love you so much
I'm looking forward to seeing the
reaction of everyone because I think I
can show you a different me than usual.
We have a birthday present from the
members!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Do you know why?
Because it's fun!
Assemble Part
What do you want to say to Hita-chan?
Hita-chan, happy birthday!
Happy 19th birthday!
You're going to be an adult in a year.
Happy birthday!
Hita-chan is always kind and funny.
She's very reliable and supportive.
I love you! Congratulations!
Hito-chan, happy birthday!
Congratulations on your 19th birthday!
You sent me a lot of pictures of shaved
ice on LINE, right?
Let's go this year!
Go!
Hito-chan is always talking to me, and
I'm always happy.
When I go out to eat with Hito-chan,
she says,
I'm always greeted by her, but her
smile is always cute.
Please continue to give me a lot of
excitement!
Bye-bye!
Hitoka, happy birthday!
I, Hitoka, Hiyori and Kanamin have been
together for 5 or 6 years in TokiSEN.
We've been together for so long that I
feel like time has flown by.
It's been a long time, but I really
enjoy being with Hitoka.
Hitoka is at the forefront of fashion
and trends.
She always tells us what's popular
these days.
She has a different expression
depending on the song and the hot
expression she shows during the live.
She's also very good-looking, and I
really respect her.
I'll be by her side from now on, so I
hope we can support each other.
Thank you for your continued support!
Hitoka! Happy birthday!
You're 19 years old, just like me.
I can't believe we're the same age.
You're so strong.
You're the closest to me.
I respect you.
What should I say?
You have something that I don't have.
I think you're a beautiful person.
I'm sure you'll have a lot to rely on
in the future.
I'll do my best to support you.
I look forward to your continued
support!
I'm glad we celebrated our birthdays
together six times.
I look forward to your continued
support!
I'm glad we celebrated our birthdays
together!
Ichigo Ichigo Ichigo Ichigo!
One more time!
Yes! One more time!
Happy birthday!
I met Hitoka when I was in 6th grade.
We've been together since then.
I didn't expect that Hitoka would be 19
years old now.
I made a lot of memories with Hitoka
during that time.
We went on a trip together.
Looking back at the picture,
we went to a lot of places.
I think Hitoka is the member who goes
to the most places with TOKISEN.
We went to a lot of places.
It's really fun, isn't it?
Hitoka!
I respect Hitoka's performance.
I love Hitoka who is always energetic,
powerful, and like the sun.
Please keep shining TOKISEN brightly.
Congratulations on your birthday!
I look forward to working with you.
I love you.
I miss you.
Every time I think of you,
I feel a strong feeling in my heart.
I'm still waiting for the rainbow-
colored bench.
The bench is getting white.
The scenery that started to look like a
love story.
I'm still waiting for someone.
Alright, let's continue on...
...Tsubakura.
It's Sewo's main game now!
Hey, I'll never forget
Under the sky with one eye open
I love you
I'm happy just by being like this
This kind of time is happiness
A rainbow-colored bench
Will never change
Bench, one, two, three, four, five